Guide to the Jan Van Dyke papers, 1964-2005 MS2111
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio-visual materials, clippings, correspondence, programs and promotional materials, 1964-2002; MS2111 Series 3; 1.25 Linear feet (Box 15, Box 14, Box 13, Box 12)
  - Audio-visual materials, clippings, correspondence, programs and promotional materials, undated (Box 13)
  - Audio-visual materials: VHS: A Dance in Two Spaces [1/2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Two tapes showing simultaneous aspects of one dance performed in the atria of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. Danced by Jan Van Dyke and Dancers in 1979. Funded by the National Endowment for the Arts.
  - Audio-visual materials: VHS: A Dance in Two Spaces [2/2], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Audio-visual materials: VHS: Waltz, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Jan Van Dyke performing Waltz (1973) at the Contemporary Dance Theater in Cincinnati in 1980.
  - Audio-visual materials: U-matic: Fleetwood Mac Suite, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Fleetwood Mac Suite (1978) danced by Jan Van Dyke and Dancers.
  - Audio-visual materials, clippings, correspondence, programs and promotional materials, undated (Box 14)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1964-1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979-2002 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Audio-visual materials, clippings, correspondence, programs and promotional materials, undated (Box 15)
  - Newspaper clippings: Peggy Lyman--Waltz, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Ceremony I (in 6 Acts), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Paradise Castle, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Ceremony II, 1976 ca. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Twilight, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Fleetwood Mac Suite, 1978 ca. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Parade on Connecticut Avenue, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: The Passenger, 1978 ca. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: A Dance in Two Spaces, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Circling, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Ella, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Programs and promotional materials, 1967-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Programs and promotional materials, 1973-1985 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Programs and promotional materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Programs, brochures, articles, 2002-2005; MS2111 Series 4; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 15)
  This series contains programs, publicity post cards, articles, and brochures that document the activities of the North Carolina Dance Project, which manages the Jan Van Dyke Dance Group. The materials date from 2002-2005.
  - Programs, brochures, articles, undated (Box 15)
  - Programs, brochures, articles, 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)